Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED], 1942-1960; 1962-1988; 1970-1986; 1; 9.33 cubic ft.
  - Program Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Program Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Program Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Program Proposals [RESTRICTED], 1973-1985 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Public Relations/Fundraising [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Public Statements [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Reception [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Reception [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Reception [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Reception Committee [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Reception Committee [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Reception - Follow-up [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Reception - Mailing List [RESTRICTED], ca. 1985 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Reception - Scroll [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Receptions [RESTRICTED], 1963-1972 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Receptions [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Report on Financial Statements [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Reports and In - house Memoranda [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Requests for Information [RESTRICTED], 1970-1979 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Resources Committee [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Resources Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Resources Committee - Cocktail Party [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Resources Committee - Cocktail Party - Board Guest Lists [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Resources Committee - Cocktail Party Follow-up [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Resumes [RESTRICTED], 1962-2004 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Retreat [RESTRICTED], 1986-1988 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Retreat [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Richards and Fenniman, Inc. - Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - RSVP - Volunteer Referral [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Samuels, Howard [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Scalare, A. Balfour [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Schwartz, Herman - Chairman, State Commission of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Search Committee [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    Contains copies of affidavits and court rulings concerning prisoners' efforts to unionize and the photocopied resume of future New Jersey governor Christine Todd Whitman.
  - Search Committee [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Search Committee [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Search Committee [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Seth Sprague Educational and Charitable Foundation [RESTRICTED], 1947-1960 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Special Committee on Sentencing [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Special Committee on Sentencing [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 9 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Speech - Talking to My Brothers about Genocide [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Standing Committees [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Standing Committees - Osborne Association and CANY [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Statement - Marijuana Decriminalization [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Tax Exempt Status [RESTRICTED], 1961-1975 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Testimony - Appointment Review of Chairman - State Commission of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Testimony - Capital Punishment [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Testimony - Juvenile Justice [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Testimony - Manhattan House of Detention [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Testimony - Minimum Standards [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Testimony - Minimum Standards, NYC Correctional Facilities [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Testimony - NYC Budget [RESTRICTED], 1984 May 11 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Testimony - NYC Jail Expansion [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Testimony - NYS Executive Advisory Committee on Sentencing [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Testimony - NYS Parole [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Testimony - NYS Proposed Executive Budget - FY 1983-84 [RESTRICTED] (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Testimony - Selection of Judges [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Testimony - Senate Codes on Definite Sentencing [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Testimony - Tufo and Mayor on Investigations [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Testimony - White Street Jail [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Volunteers [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Weintraub, Judith F. [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 10 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
- Annual Reports, 1844-1979; 2; 11 reels of 35 mm microfilm and bound copies
  This series consists exclusively of the annual reports on prison and jail conditions that the Prison Association/Correctional Association submitted to the New York State Assembly. The reports contain minutes of meetings, presidential addresses, committee reports, reports on individual prisons and prison conditions, prison reform campaigns in New York State, transcripts of testimony before the NYS legislature on pending policy measures, and lists of members and corresponding members of the Association. Reports published during the latter half of the nineteenth century chronicle the Association's role in establishing national and international prison reform organizations and conferences and furnish information about prison policies elsewhere in the United States and the world.
  Arranged chronologically. The microfilm versions are housed in the University Library Microfilm Collection, call number HV 8987 P684. Bound copies of the 1867-1878 and 1921-1969 Annual Reports are also available in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  The Annual Reports are available on microfilm in the University Library's Microfilm Collection, call number HV 8987 P684.
  Bound copies of the 1867-1878 and 1921-1969 Annual Reports are also available in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
  - Annual Reports, 1844-1850 (Reel 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1851-1866 (Reel 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1867-1870 (Reel 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1870-1886 (Reel 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1887-1895 (Reel 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1896-1909 (Reel 6)
  - Annual Reports, 1910-1914 (Reel 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1915-1924 (Reel 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1925-1940 (Reel 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1941-1960 (Reel 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1961-1979 (Reel 11)
- Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED], ca. 1915; 1962; 1974-1985; 3; 1.33 cubic ft.
  This series consists of material generated in connection with the Correctional Association's statutory responsibility for inspecting jails, prisons, and adolescent detention facilities in New York State. Documents in this series were created by the Association's General Secretary, Institutions Visiting Committee, and other personnel and include correspondence, prison visit reports, prison tour requests, memoranda, affidavits, and other court records. Also included are records concerning Correctional Association President Adam McQuillan's 1977 visit to the Southern Ohio Correctional Facility. The only document from circa 1915 is a pamphlet describing a traveling exhibition concerning the New York State prison system.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Adolescent Detention and Reception Center and Adolescent Detention Center, Rikers Island [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Albion Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Arthur Kill Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Attica Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Attica Visiting Committee [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Bayview Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Bedford Hills Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Bronx House of Detention [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn House of Detention [RESTRICTED], 1974-1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn House of Detention - Affadavits [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Chinlund v. New York City Department of Corrections [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Clinton Correctional Facility - Cancellation of Visit [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - County Jails - Dutchess [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - County Jails - Genessee [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - County Jails - Monroe [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - County Jails - Nassau [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - County Jails - Rockland [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - County Jails - Suffolk [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - County Jails - Westchester [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Eastern New York Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Fishkill Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Great Meadow Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Green Haven Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Green Haven - Complaints to Commissioner [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Guidelines for Local Visiting Committees [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - House of Detention for Men (Rikers Island) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - House of Detention for Men (Rikers Island) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - House of Detention for Men (Rikers Island) [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - House of Detention for Men (Rikers Island) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - House of Detention for Men (Rikers Island) Transfer [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Institutions Visiting Committee [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Institutions Visiting Committee [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Institutions Visiting Committee [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Institutions Visiting Committee [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Institutions Visiting Committee [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Institutions Visiting Committee - Meetings and Visits [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Institutions Visiting Committee - Seminar on Corrections [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Institutions Visiting Committee - Training, Reports, and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Institutions Visits - Donald Goff [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], ca. 1915; 1975; 1983; 1987 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - New York City Correctional Institute for Men [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - New York City Correctional Institute for Women [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - New York State Department of Corrections Guidelines [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - On the City's Master Plan (House of Detention for Men) [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
  - On the City's Master Plan - Summary [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
  - Prison-visiting Volunteers [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
  - Ossining Correctional Facility - "Sing Sing" [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
  - Queensborough Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
  - Queens House of Detention [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Queens House of Detention - Branch [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Rikers Island Hospital [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Southern Ohio Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Tables [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Taconic Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - The Tombs [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - The Tombs - Study Report [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Wallkill Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Westchester County Visiting Committee [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Woodfield Cottage and Detention Center [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 2 (3-Prison Visits Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
- Narcotics Committee Files, 1949; 1962-1972; 1975; 4; 1 cubic foot
  This series was created by the Association's Narcotics Committee, which apparently kept its records separate from other material generated by members of the Board of Directors. It contains reports, pamphlets, articles, brochures, memoranda, news clippings, and some correspondence. Among the subjects covered are: the New York State [?] Narcotics Addiction Control Commission, drug rehabilitation programs, the Federal Bureau of Narcotics, and methadone maintenance programs.
  - Marijuana, 1961-1972 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Methadone, 1965-1973 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Methadone, 1970 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Narcotics - Articles, 1962-1971; 3 folders (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Narcotics - Glasgow, 1967 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Narcotics Addiction Control Commission - New York State, 1967 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Narcotics Addiction Control Commission - Folder 1, 1966-1969 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - Narcotics Addiction Control Commission - Folder 2, 1966-1972 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - Narcotics Addiction Rehabilitation - Folder 1, 1971-1973 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 9)
  - Narcotics Addiction Rehabilitation - Folder 2, 1965-1972 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 10)
  - Narcotics Committee Correspondence, 1965-1972 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 11)
  - Narcotics, Federal Bureau of, 1949-1972 (Box 1 (4-Narcotics Committee Files), Folder 12)
- Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED], 1967-1983; 5; 1.66 cubic ft.
  This series contains material created or collected by Correctional Association staffers responsible for operating programs that furnished direct services to inmates and their families. The Association's Family Services Bureau, Legal Services Bureau, and Social Services Bureau were long-term programs that were phased out during the late 1970s and early 1980s. Programs established during the 1980s were grant-funded demonstration projects designed to encourage emulation; the Association did not have the financial resources needed to sustain long-term social service programs. Of interest particular interest is the Association's short-term program to furnish counseling services to young offenders sent to the Adolescent Reception and Detention Center on Rikers Island (1981-1982). Also of interest are the documents generated in connection with the Association's efforts to establish an Ombudsman Program (1972-1973) and the ensuing resistance of Governor Nelson Rockefeller and state corrections officials.
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Application and Contracts [RESTRICTED], 1980-1982 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Correctional Association Task Force [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Correspondence - Key, K. Michael (Counselor) [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Counseling Project [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Counselors' Reports [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Foundation Appeal [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Freggans, Richard [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Monthly Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Orientation Booklet [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Resumes/Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1980? (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Statistical Data Forms [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Status Report [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Vouchers [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Adolescent Reception and Detention Center - Women Offenders Report [RESTRICTED], 1981? (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Children of Offenders Program - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Children of Offenders Program - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Children of Offenders Program - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Children of Offenders Program - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration - Grant Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Children of Offenders Program - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration - Grant Proposal and Budget [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Family Prison Visiting Program [RESTRICTED], 1967-1974 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Family Services Bureau - Christmas [RESTRICTED], 1967-1980 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Family Services Bureau - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1970-1974 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Legal Services Bureau - Interim Reports [RESTRICTED], 1971-1974 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Legal Services Bureau - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Ombudsman [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Ombudsman - Bedford Hills [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Program and Bureau Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)